first activity you need to do to figure
out as a part of like what you want to
do and where you want to do it I mean
that's a big huge task right it's very
scary so you can kind of zoom in on it
and and look at something that's much
easier ask yourself what do you like to
do every day and if you can't answer
that question answer answer another
question what do you not like to do so I
encourage you to start writing a list
perhaps on paper a lot of the stuff I
like to do on paper and and go outside
and you know get some fresh air because
you got you know the outdoors around you
helping you um if you're a religious
person you know you might be able to
find some inspiration from whatever your
high power is and you need to start
asking yourself what are the thing what
do you like right and I have a specific
story about this so my son taught uh
kids technology for a long time while he
was with me and then he went on to teach
at a private school for a while and one
day he come home and me to me and he
said you know they are great I love them
but I have really learned something
never want a job involving
kids and I'm throwing him under the bus
here because it was a moment it was a
moment it was one of these Zen Discovery
moments and you know if you're if that's
you he would have put down you know
nothing involving kids he loved he loved
them he was good with them and
everything but he's like I don't want to
be around them I would rather if I had a
choice every day this is what I like to
do and for me that if I were to write
that down it would be you know I would
be outdoors I want to be outside which
is completely ironic uh one of the perks
that I made a video video about of an IT
career is remote work life balance which
allows you to do this biking thing so
actually believe it or not that's one of
the things that I came to understand and
that's going to lead us into another
video which is how do you match the
tasks and activities that you want to do
every day with job opportunities and and
specific employers which is going to be
next so for right now just focus on what
are those tasks discover what the tasks
are that you enjoy write them down write
them down Ponder them
pray about him meditate whatever it is
you do and think you know I really like
this oh I really like this I really like
the feeling of the keyboard under my
fingers I love to type that's me I like
music I like having music around me all
the time I like being with people I love
people if I don't have people around I
can't talk to them you don't do the
Myers Briggs saying or anything like
that you don't need that you already
know everything you need to know about
yourself and if you don't there's
probably people who love you who can
reflect back to you what the things are
that you like to do maybe you're really
real well organized maybe you know
you're any of these things and by the
way don't limit yourself to technology
at this stage of the game it's not about
getting a Tech Career it's about
figuring out what it is you want to do
and where and knowing yourself okay so
let go and just close your eyes and
write down those things that you enjoy
and just and Own It own it you got to
own it you got to be authentic to
yourself you got to trust yourself this
is the whole trust thing right you you
got you got to be able to trust yourself
to know what it is you actually want
first and this is a hard thing people
don't know what they want and so you
know you spend some time don't don't
take away from that time and after you
get those tasks and activities written
down that you
enjoy you'll do the next thing